<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Divide and Conquer on Divide and Conquer: AI and Gameplay Overhaul</title><link>https://EddieEldridge.github.io/dac-ago-docs/</link><description>Recent content in Divide and Conquer on Divide and Conquer: AI and Gameplay Overhaul</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://EddieEldridge.github.io/dac-ago-docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Changelog</title><link>https://EddieEldridge.github.io/dac-ago-docs/changelog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://EddieEldridge.github.io/dac-ago-docs/changelog/</guid><description>2nd July, 2022 Fynn go brrrr
3rd June, 2021 Lerynian go brrrr
3rd June, 2021 Lerynian go brrrr
3rd June, 2021 R3APER go brrrr
3rd June, 2020 Bill do nothing :(
3rd June, 2020 Fynn go brrrr
3rd June, 2021 Lerynian go brrrr
3rd June, 2021 R3APER go brrrr
3rd June, 2020 Bill do nothing :(
3rd June, 2020 Fynn go brrrr
3rd June, 2021 Lerynian go brrrr
3rd June, 2021 R3APER go brrrr</description></item><item><title>Credits</title><link>https://EddieEldridge.github.io/dac-ago-docs/credits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://EddieEldridge.github.io/dac-ago-docs/credits/</guid><description>Models/Textures BillBaraka For his work on Dunland, Dorwinion, Enedwaith, Mordor and many other factions
Lerynian Work on Dunland, Dorwinion, Enedwaith, Mordor and many other factions
Coma Coma for his texture work and guidance in making many of the beautiful models you see in the mod
Scripts and Bugfixes Serious Potato For his faction revive script and many other quality of life scripts
Jojo For his reversing skills, scripting and extensive animation knowledge</description></item><item><title>Dorwinion</title><link>https://EddieEldridge.github.io/dac-ago-docs/factions/dorwinion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://EddieEldridge.github.io/dac-ago-docs/factions/dorwinion/</guid><description>Starting Location Dorwinion is located in the eastern reaches of Rhovanion, bordered by the mountains and sea of Rhûn. Both of these natural features provide Dorwinion some protection from their Easterling neighbours. They begin with their capital; The Garden City (Caras Sant), the castle of the Western Gardens (Sant Annui) and the City of the Coastal Folk (Strondost).
Campaign Events The premise is Dale is asking for help to rebuild now that they feel the threat of the Easterlings, the council wants to help them while the nobles and merchants want to keep their profits.</description></item><item><title>Download</title><link>https://EddieEldridge.github.io/dac-ago-docs/download/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://EddieEldridge.github.io/dac-ago-docs/download/</guid><description> Video Tutorial Quickstart Install a clean copy of Divide and Conquer 4.6 Make a copy of your Divide_and_Conquer folder located in Medieval II Total War/mods Rename it Divide_and_Conquer_ago Drag the contents of the Medieval II Total War folder in the downloaded zip archive into your own Medieval II Total War, replacing if prompted</description></item><item><title>F.A.Q</title><link>https://EddieEldridge.github.io/dac-ago-docs/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://EddieEldridge.github.io/dac-ago-docs/faq/</guid><description>Game can&amp;rsquo;t start, issues with anti-virus The Engine Overhaul often gets detected as a Trojan by windows defender or anti-virus, to be able to play with it enabled you need to make an exclusion to the mod folder The reason it gets detected is because it works by modifying the memory of another program when you run it (Medieval 2), which is similar to what some malicious programs would do to other programs you don&amp;rsquo;t want it to happen to.</description></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://EddieEldridge.github.io/dac-ago-docs/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://EddieEldridge.github.io/dac-ago-docs/features/</guid><description>AI and Gameplay Completely overhauled campaign AI with a focus on different faction/culture specific behaviour Aggression, how likely to betray depends on what kind of faction it is. Allies help way more, they will often come to relieve a siege on one of your settlements Overhauled diplomacy and faction standings. AA start neutral to everyone even as AI, but they generally dislike everyone and hate the Dunedain nations and Mordor Made it basically impossible for the most lore breaking ceasefires/alliances/wars to happen.</description></item></channel></rss>